filmykeeday.com 2017-05-27

# Privacy Policy

Please read this Privacy Policy before accessing the website. As a result of your access and use of the website, you hereby consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, we request and advise you not to use the website. We reserve the right to revise the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check back to this Privacy Policy periodically to review any changes. Your continued access to the website will indicate your acceptance of any such changes.

Website collects some non-personal information (Read Below for detail) from visitors to the website as well as personal information from registered persons who voluntarily comment on website via facebook or any other methods.

 ** _Non-Personal Information_** collected by [www.filmykeeday.com](http://www.filmykeeday.com/) from its visitors contains:

Internet protocol (or IP) address  
Online presence  
Activity type on the website  
Browser type or domain name of the visitor  
The viewing patterns of the visitor (collected via Google Analytics)

This non-personal information is collected by the website and follows links to and from third party websites ( by Google Adsense).

Website may disclose **_This non-personal information_** (mentioned above) ** __** to its marketing partners and advertisers so that these third parties may learn the requirements and preferences of each visitor and, accordingly, serve each visitor with customized content including user-targeted advertisements. Although [www.filmykeeday.com](http://www.filmykeeday.com/) discloses such non-personal information to third parties on the condition that these third parties will not retain this non personal information or use it for any purpose other than that stated.

 **Note:** Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. ****
